Prince Prajapati

Cell (226) 202 4300

Princepn290@gmail.com



PROFILE

Technical Skills:

HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript/jQuery, MongoDB, MySQL, Python/Django, C#/ASP.NET, AWS, Azure, Google Cloud, WordPress, Web Development, Blogger, SEO

PROFILE SUMMARY

Highly organized and Developer and Blogger with over 1.5 years of experience in the coding development process. Understanding of machine learning, statistics, critical thinking with excellent practical experience using: Python, C#, JavaScript, MySQL. A result driven achiever with strong predictive modelling and data analytics skills.

Education: Diploma : Computer Programming

(Sept.2021-Apr.2023)

Employment:

Developer, Blogger: https://www.anonymous.education/ Jun 2020-Present

- Made this User-friendly blogger website by using HTML5, CSS3 and JavaScript using Visual Studio Code Editor as well WebStorm.
- Research and analyze the trending technology topics and implement in the website.
- Programmed different pages for various functionalities.
- Providing Code Structures and Solutions Python, Java and C languages.
- Implement Interviews for student help in order to jump into Tech Industry.

Internship : Assistant Team LeadTechnical Support / <u>Gao Tek</u> ,Toronto, Canada/ May 2022 – August 2022

- Coordinated with Level 1 technical support specialists to manage Agile, Azure DevOps, AWS Cloud.
- Solving almost 90% of technical issues using Terraform within 1 month of joining.
- Provided information and assisted customer with dept technical solutions at Tier 2 level.
- Promoted to Assistant Team leader to handle other Interns and trained them using Azure DevOps.
- Solved some complex software tickets without reached out to level 3 engineers.

Projects:

Project Management Project:

Build Task management using C# with ASP.NET Framework.

Can add people, who's working on tasks. As well handle all the previous and upcoming tasks. Unit testing by using methods.

Debugging and Migration to add various task and remove it.

Restaurant Management Project:

Developed Management Project using JavaScript framework jQuery and SQL Database.

Deploy to Android studio to make it available in Smart Phones.

Handle exceptions of jQuery, validations and Google Search Console Analysis.

Develop and implement Pipeline to initiate the Validation for web.